{
    "Food": [
        {
            "question": "What Tunisian food will a 40-year-old mother cook on a rainy day?\u26c8\ufe0f",
            "options": [
                "Fish & chips \ud83d\udc1f\ud83c\udf5f",
                "Vegetables noodles \ud83c\udf5c",
                "Mhamesa \ud83c\udf72"
            ],
            "answer": "Mhamesa \ud83c\udf72"
        },
        {
            "question": "You\u2019re fasting in Ramadan and can\u2019t wait for Ftour. What\u2019s the first thing most Tunisian families eat?\ud83d\udc68\ud83c\udffc\u200d\ud83d\udc69\ud83c\udffc\u200d\ud83d\udc67\ud83c\udffc\u200d\ud83d\udc66\ud83c\udffc",
            "options": [
                "Brik \ud83e\udd5f",
                "Sushi \ud83c\udf63",
                "Samsa \ud83e\udd60"
            ],
            "answer": "Brik \ud83e\udd5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "In a \ud83c\udf89Tunisian wedding\ud83c\udf89, what dish is the star of the night?",
            "options": [
                "Lablabi \ud83e\udd63",
                "Pizza Tunisienne \ud83c\udf55",
                "Couscous with meat \ud83c\udf72"
            ],
            "answer": "Couscous with meat \ud83c\udf72"
        },
        {
            "question": "On a rainy morning, what food would a construction worker eat before going to work? \u26c8\ufe0f",
            "options": [
                "Croissant \ud83e\udd50",
                "Bssisa\ud83c\udf72",
                "Dro3 \ud83e\udd63"
            ],
            "answer": "Dro3 \ud83e\udd63"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which spicy condiment\ud83e\udd75 is in almost every Tunisian dish?",
            "options": [
                "Ketchup \ud83e\udd6b",
                "Harissa \ud83c\udf36",
                "Mayonnaise \ud83e\udd5a"
            ],
            "answer": "Harissa \ud83c\udf36"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian sweet is also a symbol of hospitality and is offered to guests?\ud83c\udf6c\ud83d\ude0b",
            "options": [
                "Chocolate mousse \ud83c\udf6b",
                "Tiramisu \ud83c\udf70",
                "Baklawa \ud83e\udd6e"
            ],
            "answer": "Baklawa \ud83e\udd6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which sweet is made with dates, almonds, and often served during Ramadan?",
            "options": [
                "Brioche \ud83e\udd50",
                "Samsa",
                "Makroud \ud83e\udd6e"
            ],
            "answer": "Makroud \ud83e\udd6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian bread is traditionally baked in a clay oven?",
            "options": [
                "Tabouna \ud83e\uded3",
                "Pita bread \ud83e\uded3",
                "French baguette \ud83e\udd56"
            ],
            "answer": "Tabouna \ud83e\uded3"
        }
    ],
    "Geography": [
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian city is famous for Harissa\ud83c\udf36?",
            "options": [
                "Nabeul",
                "Tozeur",
                "Kairouan"
            ],
            "answer": "Nabeul"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian region is famous for its vast Sahara desert landscapes and oasis? \ud83c\udfdc\ufe0f",
            "options": [
                "Tozeur",
                "Bizerte",
                "Sfax"
            ],
            "answer": "Tozeur"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you want to see houses\ud83c\udfe0 built inside caves\u26f0\ufe0f, where should you go?",
            "options": [
                "Carthage",
                "Sidi Bou Sa\u00efd",
                "Matmata"
            ],
            "answer": "Matmata"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian island is famous for its sandy beaches and luxurious resorts\ud83c\udfdd\ufe0f?",
            "options": [
                "Djerba",
                "Kerkennah",
                "Galite Islands"
            ],
            "answer": "Djerba"
        },
        {
            "question": "You want the best dates in Tunisia. Which region are you heading to?\ud83e\udd14",
            "options": [
                "Gabes",
                "Touzeur",
                "Bizerte"
            ],
            "answer": "Touzeur"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian city is famous for its blue-painted doors and white streets\ud83c\udfe0\ud83d\udd35\ud83c\udf0a?",
            "options": [
                "Sidi Bou Said",
                "La Marsa",
                "Mahdia"
            ],
            "answer": "Sidi Bou Said"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ancient ruins of Carthage are located near which modern city?\ud83c\udfdb\ufe0f",
            "options": [
                "Tunis",
                "Sfax",
                "Bizerte"
            ],
            "answer": "Tunis"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian city is known for its ancient amphitheater, one of the best preserved in the world?\ud83c\udfdb\ufe0f",
            "options": [
                "El Djem",
                "Kairouan",
                "Carthage"
            ],
            "answer": "El Djem"
        }
    ],
    "Known_Celebrities": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the famous Tunisian tennis player\ud83c\udfbe known worldwide and nicknamed \u201cMinister of Happiness\u201d?",
            "options": [
                "Selima Sfar",
                "Ons Jabeur",
                "Nada Mezni Hafaiedh"
            ],
            "answer": "Ons Jabeur"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which sport brought Ahmed Jaouadi fame in Tunisia and earned him a spot representing his country at the Olympics\ud83e\udd47?",
            "options": [
                "Football \u26bd\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3",
                "Swimming \ud83c\udfca",
                "Basketball \ud83c\udfc0"
            ],
            "answer": "Swimming \ud83c\udfca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian comedian is famous for his humorous sketches and social satire? \ud83d\ude02\ud83c\udfad",
            "options": [
                "Karim Gharbi",
                "Hichem Rostom",
                "Nidhal Saadi"
            ],
            "answer": "Karim Gharbi"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which sport is most loved in Tunisia?",
            "options": [
                "Football \u26bd\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3",
                "Handball \ud83e\udd3e",
                "Basketball \ud83c\udfc0"
            ],
            "answer": "Football \u26bd\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian actress played in \ud83c\udfacEgyptian movies\ud83c\udfad and became a star across the Arab world?",
            "options": [
                "Hend Sabri",
                "Rim Riahi",
                "Julia Roberts"
            ],
            "answer": "Hend Sabri"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian singer is known for patriotic songs and folk music?",
            "options": [
                "Balti \ud83d\ude0e\ud83c\udfa4\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3",
                "Emel Mathlouthi \ud83d\udc69\u200d\ud83c\udfa4\ud83c\udfa4",
                "Hedi Jouini \ud83d\udc74\ud83c\udfa4\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3"
            ],
            "answer": "Hedi Jouini \ud83d\udc74\ud83c\udfa4\ud83c\uddf9\ud83c\uddf3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Samy Chaffai, the famous Tunisian, known for?\ud83c\udfa5\ud83c\udf0d",
            "options": [
                "Singer \ud83c\udfa4",
                "Content creator and filmmaker \ud83c\udfac",
                "Footballer \u26bd"
            ],
            "answer": "Content creator and filmmaker \ud83c\udfac"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mouna Noureddine is best known for her work in which field?\ud83c\udfad",
            "options": [
                "Politics \ud83c\udfdb\ufe0f",
                "Acting \ud83c\udfac",
                "Singing \ud83c\udfa4"
            ],
            "answer": "Acting \ud83c\udfac"
        }
    ],
    "TV_Series": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the main character of Choufli Hal\ud83e\udd2d\ud83d\ude09?",
            "options": [
                "Slimane",
                "Douja",
                "Sbou3i"
            ],
            "answer": "Sbou3i"
        },
        {
            "question": "If your mom says \u201cDon\u2019t change the channel, I\u2019m watching Choufli Hal\u201d, what do you do?",
            "options": [
                "Take the remote\ud83d\udcfa\ud83c\udf9b and run\ud83c\udfc3",
                "\ud83e\ude74Obey\ud83e\ude74",
                "Negotiate with chocolate\ud83c\udf6b"
            ],
            "answer": "\ud83e\ude74Obey\ud83e\ude74"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who plays the character of Douja in 'Choufli Hal'?\ud83d\udc69",
            "options": [
                "Sonia Ben Cheikh",
                "Dorra Zarrouk",
                "Rim Riahi"
            ],
            "answer": "Sonia Ben Cheikh"
        },
        {
            "question": "In 'Nsibti Laaziza', who drives Baboucha crazy?\ud83d\ude02",
            "options": [
                "Khmissa & El Fehim \ud83d\udc69\u200d\ud83e\uddb0\ud83d\udc68\u200d\ud83e\uddb0",
                "His customers \ud83d\udecd",
                "Bad news \ud83c\udf99"
            ],
            "answer": "Khmissa & El Fehim \ud83d\udc69\u200d\ud83e\uddb0\ud83d\udc68\u200d\ud83e\uddb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which TV series features the daily life of Tunisian families in humorous situations?\ud83c\udfe0\ud83d\ude02",
            "options": [
                "Choufli Hal \ud83e\udd2d",
                "El Khottab Al Bab \ud83c\udfe0",
                "Nsibti Laaziza \ud83d\udc8d"
            ],
            "answer": "Choufli Hal \ud83e\udd2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Tunisian TV series is famous for its Ramadan special episodes and drama?\ud83c\udf19\ud83d\udcfa",
            "options": [
                "Maktoub \ud83d\udcdc",
                "Choufli Hal \ud83e\udd2d",
                "El Khottab Al Bab \ud83c\udfe0"
            ],
            "answer": "El Khottab Al Bab \ud83c\udfe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Ammar known for in 'Bolice' besides solving crimes?\ud83d\ude02",
            "options": [
                "Always eating while on duty \ud83c\udf55",
                "Chicken wings \ud83c\udf57",
                "Being strict \ud83d\ude0e"
            ],
            "answer": "Chicken wings \ud83c\udf57"
        },
        {
            "question": "In 'Jari Ya Hamoudi', what does Hamouda do in life?",
            "options": [
                "A lawyer \u2696\ufe0f",
                "Unemployed \ud83d\ude05",
                "Fish seller \ud83d\udc1f"
            ],
            "answer": "Fish seller \ud83d\udc1f"
        }
    ],
    "Clothing": [
        {
            "question": "What is the traditional Tunisian hat, usually red and worn proudly by men, called?",
            "options": [
                "Koufia",
                "Sombrero",
                "Chechia"
            ],
            "answer": "Chechia"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the traditional Tunisian Farmla? \ud83d\udc57\u2728",
            "options": [
                "A richly decorated vest worn by women",
                "A type of traditional hat for men",
                "A Tunisian sandal style"
            ],
            "answer": "A richly decorated vest worn by women"
        },
        {
            "question": "On Eid morning\ud83d\udd4c, what will your grandpa absolutely refuse to leave the house without?",
            "options": [
                "His jogging suit",
                "His jebba",
                "His football jersey"
            ],
            "answer": "His jebba"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the veil that aunt Fadila (Choufli Hal) wears when she goes to the market?\ud83e\uddd5",
            "options": [
                "Sefsari",
                "Hijab",
                "Chechia"
            ],
            "answer": "Sefsari"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of footwear is traditionally worn with the jebba or Sefsari?\ud83d\udc5e",
            "options": [
                "Balgha",
                "Sneakers",
                "Flip-flops"
            ],
            "answer": "Balgha"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which piece of clothing is guaranteed to make a Tunisian aunt comment, 'You can\u2019t go out like that!'\ud83d\ude02",
            "options": [
                "Ripped jeans \ud83d\udc56",
                "Fancy dress \ud83d\udc57",
                "Traditional karako \ud83d\udfe3"
            ],
            "answer": "Ripped jeans \ud83d\udc56"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is a 'Barnous' in Tunisia?\ud83e\udde5",
            "options": [
                "A traditional hooded cloak worn by men",
                "A type of hat",
                "A sandal style"
            ],
            "answer": "A traditional hooded cloak worn by men"
        },
        {
            "question": "It's your cousin's wedding\u2014what's the first thing that comes to your mind to wear at her Henna party?\ud83d\udc83",
            "options": [
                "Blouza and Fouta",
                "Green dress",
                "A pair of jeans"
            ],
            "answer": "Blouza and Fouta"
        }
    ]
}